

PROFILE

I' am Faizal Jaleel, i have experienced in finance and administration works doing in India and Maldives .to achieve a professional growth in this both fields and gaining knowledge in finance and sales. I am looking forward to join a vibrant and exciting organization where I can utilize my skills in Good performance

CONTACT DETAILS

RAHATH MANZIL AEROM SOUTH, THADICADU P.O ANCHAL, KOLLAM, PHONE:+91 9895062337 (Whats apps)

+960 9138123(viber)

Email: faizaljaleel2337@gmail.com

LinkedIn: faizaljaleel2337

PROFESSIONAL SKILL

Financial control
Business tax works
Book keeping
Over all business monitoring
Leadership skill
Export import business managing
Presentation skill
Office administration skill
Training & development

IT Skills

Sap fico End User Quick book Tally ERP 9 MS office package Adobe photoshop Adaptable to new ERP accounting Software

FAIZAL JALEEL

EDUCATION

Bachelor of commerce (Computer application)

H M arts and science college Muvattupuzha, Kerala, university: Mahatma Gandhi university kottayam, Kerala, India

2015-2018

Senior Secondary (science group)

Thadicadu higher secondary school, Thadicadu, Anchal, Kollam

Board: board of higher secondary education, Tiruvanthapuram, Kerala

2014

10th (Matriculation)

Govt higher secondary school west, Anchal, Kollam, Kerala

Board: board of public examination, Tiruvanthapuram, Kerala 2012

Certificate in Sap fico power user

Cokonet technologies ulloor, Trivandrum, Kerala Certified in 2018

Certificate in Tally

Cokonet technologies ulloor, Trivandrum, Kerala Certified in 2018

Certificate in Computer operation

G. Tech computer education Anchal, Kollam, Kerala Certified in 2008

WORK EXPERIENCE

Global talent Maldives Pvt Ltd (k. Male, Maldives) [Accountant cum Administrator]

2018 Dec - 2021 Jan

Cokonet Technologies [Accounts payable] (Ulloor, Trivandrum)

May 2018-Nov 2018

Margin free super shopee [sales man] (Muvattupuzha, Ernakulam)

JAN 2016- JAN 2018

JOB PROFILE

- Prepare and maintain accounting journals, ledgers and other financial records
- Supporting bills and reports are documents wise filling entering all docs include quotation, sales bills preparing, collection entering, purchase order, debit note, credit note, delivery note preparation etc.
- preparation of daily cash report, cheque statement, petty cash statement and assure liquidity position of the company
- manage A/R, A/P & outstanding by reconciling of customers/vendors accounts, & maintain ageing reports, and contacting customers for due dated invoices maintains and balances Banks & subsidiary accounts by verifying, allocating, posting entries, those accounts reconciling in moth wise transactions clearing on day to day wise; resolving discrepancies
- prepare inventory ledger, stock register and physical stock verification and inventory controlling
- Develop, manage and maintain comprehensive Payroll records & employee benefits by calculating deductions and earnings
- managing and preparing Maldives expatiate visa online works and preparing and submitting Maldives trade and license work like Govt office in Maldives
- Perform periodical closing procedures and closing related duties
- Maintain and preparing chart of accounts and prepare yearly
 financial statements such as trial balance, detailed statement of
 expense, notes of financial statement, cash flow statement,
 statement of equity and s hares, profit and loss account, balance
 sheet also quarterly prepare MIS report for management and
 outstanding statement report making for sales teams
- Supervision of team and people management in line with the HR tools and policies
- Organize the daily work of team including incorporation new task in the team
- Lead assigned engagement including planning, budgeting, client relationship management and delegating of staff monitor and report out of scope of time
- maintaining and recording monthly accruals, Prepaid, differed, depreciation, amortization, provisions and other adjustments on monthly basis
- prepare audit schedules and working closely with the auditors to ensure that the auditing is completed the time

- to manage the customer relation, maintain and handling and controlling and promote products in market via social medias and by face to face
- preparing importing shipment docs and clearing importing goods by sea and air shipment and payment clearing for govt bodies in Maldives
- supervise warehouse operation and oversee the employee
- responsible for importing shipment of goods and store them in an organized manner
- provide employee training and feedback, making schedules, oversee maintenance and stock control
- · sorting of all the importing goods
- · performed internal auditing
- performed general office administration responsibilities

PERSONAL INTERESTS

- Driving
- Food preparing
- Watching business blogs and movies
- Playing badminton, cricket
- Researching new business topics
- Reading books

Language Known:

- English (full working proficiancy)
- Malayalam (native proficiancy)
- Tamil (limited proficaincy)
- Devehi (limited proficiancy)

Personal Details:

Father Name : Muhammed Jaleel Mother Name : Athabiya Fathima

DOB: 4th Jan 1996 Nationality : Indian Pass Port No: P1803926

Gender: Male

Martail Status: Single

Reference:

Reference can be provided on demand